// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "5–[4–{3–(3–3–6)}] is equal to :",
        answer: "10",
        options: [
            "10",
            "6",
            "4",
            "0"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The value of 25 – 5 [2 + 3 (2 – 2 (5 – 3) + 5) – 10] ÷ 4 is :",
        answer: "23.75",
        options: [
            "5",
            "23.25",
            "23.75",
            " 25"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Simplify : [0.9 – {2.3 – 3.2 – (7.1 – 5.4 – 3.5)}]",
        answer: "0",
        options: [
            "0.18",
            "1.8",
            "0",
            "2.6"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "The sum of the cubes of the numbers 22, –15 and –7 is equal to",
        answer: "6930",
        options: [
            "6930",
            "9630",
            "3",
            "0"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "A train is travelling at the rate of 45km/hr. How many seconds it will take to cover a distance of 4 5 km ?",
        answer: "64 sec.",
        options: [
            "36 sec.",
            "64 sec.",
            "90 sec.",
            "120 sec"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The speed of a bus is 72 km/hr. The distance covered by the bus in 5 seconds is",
        answer: "100 m",
        options: [
            "100 m",
            "60 m",
            "50 m",
            "74.5 m"
        ]
    },


    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The degree measure of 1 radian (taking π= 22/7 ) is:",
        answer: "57°16’22”(approx.)",
        options: [
            "57°61’22”(approx.)",
            "57°16’22”(approx.)",
            "57°22’16”(approx.)",
            "57°32’16”(approx.)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "If a : b = 7 : 9 and b : c=15 : 7, then what is a : c?",
        answer: "5 : 3",
        options: [
            "5 : 3",
            "3 : 5",
            "7 : 21",
            "7 : 15"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "If A : B = 2 : 3, B : C = 2 : 4 and C : D = 2 : 5, then A : D is equal to :",
        answer: "2 : 15",
        options: [
            "2 : 15",
            "2 : 5",
            "1 : 5",
            "3 : 5"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "If x : y = 2 : 5, then (5x + 3y) : (5x – 3y) is equal to",
        answer: "-5",
        options: [
            "5",
            "3",
            "-3",
            "-5"
        ]
    },
];